The reason why I'm mad is because you niggas think I'm dumb.
You think we're stupid.
I don't give a flying fuck what you believe, nigga.
Believing political ideologies are one of those things that are very interesting and should be explored openly.
We can't even do that here because you niggas use communists as an insult.
You don't even know what communism is.
Or socialism or capitalism for that matter or any other ism that denotes a political ideology because you're encouraged to not think about those as actual perspectives.
Yeah, just so it's just a little word to you.
So to trigger word.
So and the reason why is because it really takes an honest understanding of those things to try to have an honest conversation about them.
These people also knew.
Yeah, nuance, nuance.
Niggas don't got these people are not here to do that nerve in their fucking body.
These people are not here to do that.
And the thing is, we allowed so many of these lying ass niggas to get away with acting like they're just being objective, neutral and trying to have a spirited conversation when all they've done is platform liars, bigots, people who know that they're lying.
People who have made entire careers out of being the one nigga in the field who's a conspiracy theorist, who's a liar.
Joe Rogan was doing episodes.
Probably has a good 200 maybe episodes of people who have no fucking qualification speaking on some scientific theory thing.
Just yapping.
Just yapping down the rabbit hole.
And millions of people are eating that shit the fuck up.
I'm wondering why disinformation and misinformation is the topic of the day.
Why it feels like we're running around with our heads on fire because we're constantly trying to overcorrect for grown ass niggas who are still being lied to and still buying fucking lies.
Yeah.
That's why this shit matters.